Just because the Police let you out
doesn't mean you didn't kill anyone.
They'll soon find evidence
to prove you're the killer.
If you piss me off, I'll kill you as well.
At the scene in Wan Mei Village
the clothing fiber we found
on the sugarcane,
the suspected murder weapon,
matched the jacket we found in your room.
Your helper Law Suet-chau
and Leung Yuet-ping both confirmed
the night you identified the body,
you were wearing that jacket.
We asked Tang Heung-nam,
he confirmed on October 15,
the night Cheung Siu-chung died,
he saw you bought sugarcane,
he drove you to Wan Mei Village
and drove you home after 11p.m., right?
Cheung Wang-chi also confirmed
you threw away Cheung Siu-chung's
smart watch,
which recorded his time of death
was at 12:05a.m.
Which means, he was already 21 years old
and was entitled to inherit
Cheung Kin-kwok's estate.
Because you were left out of the will,
you threw away the watch,
so nobody would know, is that right?
That night you went to see
Cheung Siu-chung at Wan Mei Village,
what exactly did you do?
That night...I wanted to stop Chung
from giving away Kin-kwok's assets.
But when I arrived,
I found out he already
made the arrangements.
I set up a trust fund,
Mom will get the house...
What? The tramp gets the house?
No, Grandma! Only on the condition
you and Dad have both passed away,
before it can be rented or sold.
I don't care. She can't have the house.
He just wouldn't listen.
I started scolding him and he kept
stepping back,
until he ran into the cabinet
and he hit his head.
You were so angry at the time,
did you kill him?
No! I did not.
He already got up when I left.
Did you give him sugarcane?
No, he ate it himself.
It was after 11p.m. when Nam drove me home.
If you said his watched stopped at 12:05,
I had nothing to do with his death.
Why didn't you tell us you were
at the village house?
I bought him sugarcane.
I didn't want you to suspect me.
So I said nothing.
I checked...
Cheung Siu-chung's smart watch is
an analog model
that can be linked to the watch company's
cloud storage.
The user's health information
such as heartbeat and blood pressure
can be recorded in cloud storage.
It can be used individually without
connecting to the mobile phone.
Though the watch stopped at 12:05a.m.,
the medical examiner estimated
the time of death to be
between 11p.m. on October 15 and
1a.m. on October 16.
Which means even if Tang Suk-han
left after 11p.m.,
she still could have killed
Cheung Siu-chung.
Check with the smart watch company,
to see when exactly Cheung Siu-chung's
heart stop beating.
Assume Tang Suk-han killed Cheung Siu-chung,
it was in a fit of rage.
When she found the watch
Cheung Tai-di dropped,
she realized it stopped at 12:05.
If Tang Suk-han really killed
Cheung Siu-chung,
it's likely she destroyed
the second trust fund document.
Though she's a prime suspect,
we don't have any solid proof.
We still must let her go.
Right!
The Police took old Mrs. Cheung
back to the Police station.
I heard it's about Chung's death.
The cops suspect she killed Chung?
Why would she kill her grandson?
Didn't you know?
No!
What? No wonder!
Must be. What else would they want with her?
Her cooking?
The Chief seemed so upright.
He certainly kept it in the family.
Men like it handy.
What?
Young Mrs. Cheung is still charming.
But who could commit incest?
Exactly!
Your turn!
Look, I'm not afraid to speak my mind.
The Chief's wife is old and over the hill.
She thinks because she's the Chief's wife,
she's entitled to bully others.
But young Mrs. Cheung is so much
more amiable.
Naturally, the Chief prefers the
daughter-in-law over the wife.
Don't say that...
That's not right...
How could you...
I felt bad that old Mrs. Cheung was
betrayed by her husband and daughter-in-law,
but it wasn't Chung's fault.
Chung was so adorable,
how could she do it? That's so cruel!
That's true...
So sad...
I must go get groceries...
What?
Look at the time...
I have won enough...
I need to pick up my grandson from school.
How did they know?
This is so humiliating.
It wasn't me. I said nothing.
People nowadays can't tell right from wrong.
It was that tramp's fault,
but they sounded like I made a mistake.
What has the world come to?
In the mourning hall,
I will get seven Taoist priests and
two musicians
for the Breaking of the Gates of Hell and
Crossing the Bridge rituals.
Leung Yuet-ping, it must be you.
You badmouthed me in front of the villagers
and told them I deserved what I got.
You seduced my husband. You're the tramp.
This is nothing to be proud of.
Why would I tell anyone?
Please don't argue.
And you! Why did you tell the Police
about us?
They questioned me. I had to tell them.
But I didn't tell anyone else.
Maybe when the Police was conducting
their investigation,
the villagers found out on their own.
You just didn't want people to know
you went to see Chung in the village house.
You were afraid people would
find out what you did.
I told you I didn't kill Chung.
He really pissed me off
and I shoved him into the cabinet.
But he was still alive when I left.
Just because the Police let you out
doesn't mean you didn't kill anyone.
They'll soon find evidence
to prove you're the killer.
Brother Nam, let's talk outside.
I don't want to be in the same room
with a murderer.
You better get out!
If you piss me off, I'll kill you as well.
Have you seen your father?
No.
You know nothing.
Chi...
Cuckold...
It suits you...
Chi...
Let's go...
Why did you bully my son?
Chi is a cuckold. See? He looks great!
Delete that! Go to Hell!
You better pay for my phone.
Get lost or I'll crush you!
You're a lunatic!
I'll kill you if you bully Chi again.
I will kill you!
Chi, are you OK?
It hurts...
You need someone to watch over you.
Let's go home and I'll put something on it.
Where the hell is Chau?
This is so infuriating!
I told you not to go out by yourself.
When I'm not here, no one will
keep an eye on you.
To think I can count on that tramp
to carry on the family line
and Chung would take care of you.
Nothing is going as planned
and we ended up with an illegitimate son.
Don't be mad, Mom.
I'll avoid them from now on.
You're gullible because of your kind heart.
Tell me, I threw away Chung's watch,
why did you put it back in my room?
I saw you throw away Chung B's watch,
I got it back for you.
That's not how you usually talk.
Are you reciting these lines?
I saw you throw away Chung B's watch,
I got it back for you.
What about the jacket?
Madam Han!
What?
Your feng shui jade gourd is broken.
Go take a look!
How did that happen?
Yes!
Oh dear, what happened?
I don't know. I was working in the kitchen
I heard a bang and came to take a look.
Maybe the rats knocked it down?
Don't! You may cut yourself!
I wonder if it can be fixed.
Not if it's shattered like this.
I had this jade gourd for decades.
Let's hope breaking it can block
my bad luck.
Clean it up.
OK!
Chi...
What is it?
What are you doing here?
This is my room.
Why can't I be here?
Mom, please go away.
You complain I don't take good enough
care of Chi.
Now, I'm doing my best. See?
Honey...
Please leave us alone.
Morning, Madam Han.
Where's Chi?
It's late. They didn't come down
for breakfast?
No...
Where are you going so early
with a travel bag?
Chi is still in bed?
He was up all night.
I'm going up to him.
Don't bother. He left early with me.
He's not in his room.
Where did he go?
Since I'm such an eyesore to you,
we're moving out.
If you want to leave, go ahead.
Why did you bring Chi with you?
You're funny. He's my husband.
Of course we must move together.
Never break up a couple.
How vicious of you!
You're hiding him and won't let me see him.
Why would I need to hide him?
He's my husband, would I kidnap him?
If he wants to see you, he will contact you.
Madam Han, you want breakfast?
What's wrong with you? You're so clumsy!
I'm sorry! I...I'll get you a towel.
I'm back.
Honey, where were you?
You were gone after I finished wee wee.
I bought you new coloring pens and
a coloring book.
Then I saw this bag. Isn't it pretty?
I don't want to do coloring.
I want to go to the DAC. I missed Mom.
I already told you,
Father and Chung B are gone,
Mother must be very upset.
She wanted to stay in this
Presidential Suite of the hotel.
But we must stay here for a month
before we can book it.
You want Mother to be happy, right?
I want Mom to be happy.
But...why must we hide?
Why can't we go back to the DAC?
And why... no phone calls?
Because it's a surprise.
Just think, if Mother asks you,
you're likely to tell her everything.
She'll bring you home
and ruin our whole plan, right?
Come...see what I got you.
See? It's a big car.
Color pencils...look, coloring book.
That will keep you busy for a month.
So big...
Wait...stop playing.
What about your homework?
Did you memorize it?
Yes!
I'll test you.
Why did you put Chung B's watch
in Mother's room?
I booked the mourning hall for Chung
on November 2.
The next day, the body will go into storage.
The feng shui master said
he'll pick another auspicious day
for his burial.
He will be buried in the family cemetery.
Wait! I want Chung buried at sea.
What?
Why?
Why bury him at sea?
Mother, I know you're now
the head of the family,
and I should respect you.
But Chung is a member of the Cheung family,
he should be buried with Father and
his ancestors.
I know you hate Chung,
but I can't let him die without
a burial place.
I have my reasons.
I don't need to explain myself.
You're his grandmother, but I'm his mother.
Please let me make this decision for him.
I don't want Chung to suffer anymore.
Cousin Han, Chung had an epilepsy attack
when he was young and almost drowned.
He was afraid of water all his life.
If you bury him at sea,
he'll never find peace.
That's right!
What gives?
A proper burial beats burial at sea...
This is outrageous!
Shut up, all of you!
Don't let this woman con you with
her pathetic act.
She only seems becoming,
she's vicious inside.
We all have skeletons in the closet.
Butt out of our family business.
You can't say that.
That's right!
We're all from the Cheung ancestors.
The Chief left us,
his business is our business, right?
That's right...
Exactly!
Mother, go ahead and hate me.
But Chung had nothing to do with this.
Whatever reason killed him,
he's no longer with us,
please go easy on him.
That's right!
Quit you act! Go to Hell!
You hit her?!
That's outrageous!
How could you?
This is not right...
Cousin Han, why did you hit her?
Don't you get rough...
You have no proof...
Let's go!
Where are you taking her?
Anywhere we want.
You should not get rough...
That's outrageous!
You'll get your retribution...
Let go of me!
That's enough, Grandma! Will you calm down?
People will think you're the baddie
if you keep this up.
I don't care!
That tramp sheds a few tears
and everyone is on her side.
There's no justice in this world.
Miss Ma!
Something came up at home.
I wish to pick up Cheung Wang Chi early.
Mrs. Cheung already withdrew
Cheung Wang Chi from class this morning.
Did she say which DAC she's taking him?
No, she didn't.
Excuse me, I have work to do.
(Tap Tung Island)
Mom?
You think my drawing...
will get posted on the board?
Of course! It's so pretty.
Hello?
Chau?
Yes, Madam Han?
Remember a long time ago,
I went to Tap Tung Island.
I forgot how to get there.
Do you know the way? Can you take me?
I don't know.
I'm getting groceries now. I can't take you.
Forget it!
Get me the file from four years ago.
Go on in.
Hello, Grandma? What is it?
I want to go to Tap Tung Island.
Can you tell me how to get there?
Take a taxi to Wong Shek Pier
and take the ferry from there.
Why do you want to go there?
Nothing. Just for a walk.
You conned me to Tap Tung Island.
They don't have seafood.
(A year ago)
But we had a good time, right?
It's pretty out here.
Better than fighting with Mom at home.
You're so good at cheering people up.
I know you're a good kid.
Whatever makes you happy, Grandma.
(The night of the incident)
It's been five days. Where are you?
Hello, Chung? Have you eaten?
Yes!
The trust fund Mr. Mok set up for you
will be effective from the day
you specified.
Trust fund?
OK! Good.
Be careful, bye.
If you take a taxi,
tell the driver No. 38 Wan Mei Village.
What trust fund?
I wonder how Chung will divide up the money?
I better go talk to him.
Chung likes sugarcanes.
Hi, Wong Kee!
Yes?
I want a sugarcane.
Cousin Han, what are you getting
at this late hour?
Fancy running into you.
Are you busy?
I need you to take me somewhere.
Take me to Wan Mei Village.
Wan Mei Village?
I don't know my way there.
What?
Hang on...
OK!
This should be it.
Wait for me in the car.
Call me.
Grandma? How did you find me?
You're not mad at me anymore?
Am I not welcome here?
You're always welcome! Come on in!
I bought your favorite sugarcane.
Thanks, Grandma!
A lot happened lately
and I'm in a foul mood.
I didn't mean to yell at you.
It's OK. As long as you're not
mad at me anymore.
Good boy!
You're still young.
You should seek my advice, OK?
For instance, the inheritance...
I got it all sorted out.
I set up a trust fund,
Mom will get the house...
What? The tramp gets the house?
No, only on the condition
you and Dad have both passed away,
before it can be rented or sold.
I don't care. I don't want that tramp
to get the house.
I want you to change the trust fund.
This arrangement is to ensure
no more arguments.
I'll explain to all of you tomorrow.
Don't be angry.
Have some sugarcane, it's sweet.
The sight of you eating sugarcane
infuriates me.
You remind me of Grandpa.
Go to Hell! I raised a traitor!
You're an ingrate like him!
No, Grandma!
Don't call me Grandma!
You can't get anything done.
Chung!
Grandma, trust me. This is the best way.
Why won't you listen?
Let's go home.
If Chung comes home tomorrow to
announce the trust fund,
there'll be big trouble.
How can I change his mind?
Hello?
Grandma? Something happened to Chung.
What is it?
The paramedics are trying to revive him.
I called Mom and Dad,
but they're not picking up.
Can you go wake them up?
Open the door! Get up!
What is it?
Tai-di just called.
Something bad happened to Chung.
What?
They're giving him emergency resuscitation.
The paramedics suspect when Cheung Siu-chung
was eating sugarcane,
scraps went inside his trachea by mistake
and caused him to suffocate.
Chung, I'm so sorry!
If I didn't bring you sugarcane,
you wouldn't have choked on it.
Chung's watch?
If Mr. Cheung Siu-chung was 21 years old,
he was entitled to inherit the estate.
12:05a.m.?
I shouldn't have picked up the watch.
Then I wouldn't be in trouble.
Grandma, what are they doing?
They're giving a family member
a burial at sea.
What's that?
It means to scatter the ashes at sea.
Grandma, I want a burial at sea.
Touch wood! Don't talk nonsense.
I'm serious. I love swimming.
But Mom won't let me because of my spasm.
If I'm buried at sea,
then I can swim freely.
You want bean curd pudding?
No, excuse me...do you know
where they scatter ashes at sea?
I'm not sure.
But people usually take the boat
and go west.
You need to bury someone at sea?
My grandson passed away.
I promised to bury him at sea.
I want to take a look at his resting place.
Go that way and you can see it.
Should I go this way or this way?
Oh no. Which way should I go?
Hello, Auntie Chau? Is this important?
I'm in a meeting.
Is Madam Han home for dinner?
I called her several times
but she didn't pick up.
Didn't you go to Tap Tung Island with her?
No, I have too much work to do.
OK, I'll try to find her.
The number you dialed cannot be reached.
Please call again later...
Ms. Cheung, Anson is asking for you.
OK!
Grandma, where are you? Call me back.
I talked for ten minutes. About what?
Follow up is important.
I don't need to remind you of the stamping.
Before we go to court,
I already agreed with the opposing counsel
to settle.
OK!
Anson, I'm sorry!
There's something urgent at home.
Can I leave early?
No problem!
Great. Thanks!
Call me if you need me.
OK!
Thanks a lot!
Excuse me...have you seen her?
Yes! She said she wanted her grandson
to be buried at sea
and came to check out the surroundings.
She went that way.
Great! Thank you!
No signal?
It's Tai-di! Hello, Tai-di?
Grandma, where are you?
I sprained my ankle.
I don't know where I am.
Calm down. Describe your surroundings.
Trees...nothing but trees.
I don't know where I am.
Come get me! Hurry...Hello?
Hello, Grandma?
Oh dear! The phone went dead.
What will happen now?
Help...Help...
Grandma!
What took you so long?
Where are you hurt?
I sprained my foot.
Let me see...
You probably can't walk. I'll carry you.
How? You're so skinny?
You better not drop me on the ground.
Hurry! You're so slow.
You're barely moving in those high heels.
If we missed the last ferry,
we won't get home.
Oh dear! Look...there goes the last ferry!
Why are you so slow?
How can you be a lawyer?
Grandma, I love swimming.
I want a burial at sea.
Touch wood! Don't talk nonsense!
You must follow the family tradition
and be buried in the family cemetery.
Let's go take the ferry...
Bite your tongue! Don't talk nonsense!
No, I really love swimming.
That's why I want to be buried at sea.
Here!
What is it?
Honey lemon with tangerine peel.
You asked for it.
It's too sour!
I'll fix you something to eat.
I saw you throw away the watch,
I'm scared...it's so hard...
Make sure you memorize the lines.
They'll come in handy.
This is called planning ahead.
I have had enough for over 20 years.
Use your hand and scrub.
Just because you married into this family,
doesn't mean you're precious.
Kin-kwok has the final say in this house
and Chi is most precious.
You take good care of him,
you're the young lady of the house.
If not, you're no different from the maid.
Father, what must I do
before Mother will be satisfied?
Don't do this...
Listen, at the next meeting of
the village office,
I'll bring you along.
You can help out over there
and when you're done,
go shopping and take a break, OK?
Really, Father?
Yes...
Thank you, Father.
Kin-kwok has the final say in this house.
Remember I told you not to touch me
right there?
It hurts when you touch me.
I'll be gentle.
It still hurts.
If you love me, don't touch me there.
You don't want to hurt me, right?
Right.
Turn over that way.
Father, what are you doing?
Auntie Chau is here.
No, Father! Did you wear a condom?
I ran out.
You can't...
Why not? I always can...
What now? I'm pregnant!
You are? Mine?
Of course! Chi never touched me.
I don't care, I'm getting an abortion.
Don't do that...
Just say it's Chi's baby.
Chi is mentally challenged,
if you give him a smart son,
I will have an heir.
I married Chi to take care of him.
I have no intention to bear child.
If you give me a son,
I'll make it worthwhile for you.
I'll give you $500K to start.
Another $5M after the baby is born.
You can do anything you want after that.
You promised me $5M after
the baby is born.
What's the meaning of $50K?
When you married Chi, you had no
intention to bear child.
It's a job and you're after money.
Of course! You can't be so naive
to think I married him for his personality.
I have no hope for Chi.
Let me ask you,
what kind of employer would pay
his employee the whole lump sum?
Relax! You'll get your $5M...
in installments.
You're Chung's Mom and Chi's wife.
As long as you stay in this family,
you'll get paid by month.
The longer you stay, the more you make.
You didn't keep your end of the bargain.
I'll expose you.
Oh, I'm so scared. This is a business deal.
You shoot off your mouth,
we'll both be ruined.
Why not go for a win-win situation?
If you stay and please me,
this house will be yours, understand?
Chung is my son with your husband,
my father-in-law.
What?
Chung is my son with your husband,
my father-in-law.
I hate you. Why did you do it?
Chung...
Listen to me.
No!
I don't want to listen.
You had Chung B with Dad?
You made me a cuckold!
I didn't mean to. Father forced me...
What?
One time when nobody was home,
Father forced me to sleep with him.
I was pregnant with Chung
but didn't dare tell you.
I was afraid you'd kick me out.
That's why every time you touch me,
I would think of your father...
It hasn't been easy for me.
That's why I lied to you. I'm sorry.
I'm not angry with you, or Chung B.
Really? Then you must protect me.
You must listen to me
and say anything I want you to say.
OK!
(One day before the incident)
Chung, even if you give me the house,
Grandma will live there till she dies
before I can sell or rent.
What if I die before she does?
Then I'll get nothing.
You won't die before she does.
I want the family to be together.
No! Stay right there! We must sort this out.
I don't want to listen to you.
Chung...
I don't want to see you anymore.
Why are you doing this to me?
Chung's watch?
After Mom took back her jacket...
I heard a noise in the trash
and I saw Chung B's watch.
Your mother threw away the jacket
and the watch.
You picked up the jacket
and the watch fell into the trash can.
Maybe Mom was angry with Chung B
and threw away the watch along with
the jacket.
I didn't want to part with it,
and picked it up.
Tai-di said she dropped the watch.
The old hag found it but didn't say anything
and secretly threw it away.
She obviously had something to hide.
I'd be letting myself down
if I didn't frame you.
Good job, Chi!
Thanks to you, we get to keep
Chung B's watch.
Your mother must be furious
that's why she threw away the watch.
When she gets over being angry with Chung B,
she'll regret that she threw the watch away.
I'll keep it for her
and give it back when she's not angry.
That's not a good idea.
What if you lost the watch?
You should keep it where she can't find it.
In a drawer in her room...
Remember it was your idea
and you never told me.
We must keep it a secret.
OK!
She kept the jacket, where is it?
Wait...I have one too.
You like my jacket?
It's a gift from a friend.
I'll wear it to a friend's dinner party.
It's very nice. Look at the material. See?
What is it doing here?
Tell me, I threw away Chung's watch,
why did you put it back in my room?
Rats! I can't let her
badger Chi with questions.
I saw you throw away Chung B's watch...
Auntie Chau...
What is it?
Go upstairs and tell Madam Han
her feng shui jade gourd fell and broke
You'll get an extra $1,000 every month.
What about the jacket?
Madam Han!
Your feng shui jade gourd is broken.
How did that happen?
Yes!
Chi!
Honey?
Take off your clothes.
What?
Hurry! Take them off...
Can we kiss kiss?
Yes, but you must do the bunny hop
until I tell you to stop.
Hurry...
Chi...
What is it?
What are you doing here?
This is my room.
Why can't I be here?
Mom, please go away.
Please leave us alone.
Chi, Father and Chung both died.
Mother is heartbroken.
You want to cheer her up, right?
I have a plan.
But you must get up early
tomorrow morning and pack.
We'll move to a hotel for a month.
Can you do that?
Yes. What's the plan?
I'll tell you later.
As long as I can fool this idiot,
soon, when Chung's trust fund
comes into effect,
it'll be harvest time for me.
I'll kick out this lot of idiots
and start my second life.
Chi!
Mom, I missed you.
Cousin Han, I thought you're not coming.
If I said I'm coming, I won't see Chi.
When you asked me yesterday
whether I'll attend the funeral,
I knew you'd tip her off.
If I said I'm coming,
someone won't let me see Chi.
Am I right?
You're overthinking.
Madam Han, I didn't betray you.
Mom, what did you say? I don't understand.
There's something I don't understand either.
I want to ask you...come with me.
I have something to ask you,
you better answer me honestly.
Why did you put the jacket and
the watch in my room?
Who told you to do it?
I only put the watch...no jacket.
Not you? Then who was it?
I don't know. You threw it away
then you took it back.
I thought you wanted to keep it.
Who taught you to put the watch in my room?
Your wife?
No, you threw it out.
I thought when you're not angry with Chung B
you might want it back.
So I put it back for you.
That woman brainwashed you.
Where are you staying?
I'll help you pack. Come home with me.
I can't tell you.
Chi...
Why not...
Go back inside.
I want to talk to you.
What is it?
I have always wanted to hit you. Period.
You...
I won't go easy on you...
No, Mother...
I'll kill you...
Don't hit me...
I'll get you for this...
Stop hitting me...
Stop! What's going on?
This tramp hit me!
No, Mother was wrong about me...
I wanted to explain and she slapped me.
Then she chased me out
and wanted to hit me again.
You seduced my husband
and want to steal the inheritance.
She told my son to put the watch in my room
to frame me for killing my grandson.
How vicious of you!
No...she made that up!
What?
She hit me in front of the
villagers earlier.
Now she wants to kill me.
Stop framing me!
Calm down!
Chung's head hit the cabinet because of you!
You shoved him into the glass cabinet.
You meant to kill him.
You should be dead of all people!
Enough!
We'll conduct the investigation
to find the killer.
We came here to tell you something.
According to the record of
Cheung Siu-chung's smart watch company,
his heartbeat stopped at 12:05a.m.
on October 16.
He was 21 years old when he died,
which means he was entitled to inherit
Cheung Kin-kwok's estate.
If Chung was entitled to the inheritance,
this tramp will get all the money!